collegenews.com 2017-05-09

# Privacy Policy & User Agreement - College News

This privacy policy is applicable to the Web site located at the domain “www.collegenews.com” and any other sites within the College News network which may link to this privacy policy (collectively, the “Site"). We do not collect any personal identifying information from users who are browsing the public areas of our Web site. Users of the public areas of our Website browse anonymously. We will not review the use of publicly accessible College News web sites by individual users unless this information will assist us in troubleshooting individual problems. College News will also review this information if a user’s account is associated with:

• Attempts to violate security of College News computer networks  
• Activity that degrades the performance of College News Websites  
• Activity that might be related to copyright violations

All material on the Website “www.collegenews.com,” and any other sites within the College News network, are copyright © College News, 2012.

Applicable laws (choice of venue and forum)  
Use of this web site shall in all respects be governed by the laws of the state of Illinois, U.S., regardless of the laws that might be applicable under principles of conflicts of law. The parties agree that the Illinois courts located in Cook county, Illinois, shall have exclusive jurisdiction over all controversies arising under this agreement and agree that venue is proper only in those courts.

Online Privacy Policy for Identifying Information  
College News collects personally identifying information and data about individuals, their company, and the company’s demographics ("personally identifying information and data") including when you provide information to College News, such as when you register or sign up for any of our products such as publications, subscriptions, e-mails, contests, surveys, newsletters, memberships, webcasts, podcasts, online seminars, conferences and other communications with College News.

College News, or third party partners may place a “cookie” in the browser files of a user’s computer. The cookie itself does not contain any personally identifying information, except when such information has been supplied by a subscriber or registered user. If you have registered with College News, the information in your “cookie” may be used to provide a more personalized experience on our Web site.

Postal addresses, and other personally identifying information and data will be used to promote College News and other products and services, and may be rented and/or licensed to selected outside firms for promotional purposes. Offers for which the personally identifying information and data are rented and/or licensed for use and the users are required to target their offers carefully.

Telephone numbers of College News print subscribers are used by College News to collect re-qualification data and may be used by College News affiliates and it’s advertisers for promotional purposes. College News may rent and/or license for use phone numbers to select outside firms for promotional purposes. Offers for which the numbers are rented and/or licensed for use are required to target their offers carefully.

Fax numbers of College News print subscribers are used by College News to collect re-qualification data and may be used for surveys for College News and third parties. Except as set forth in this policy, no fax numbers are rented and/or licensed to outside firms.

E-mail addresses of Collegenews.com subscribers are used for re-qualification purposes. These e-mail addresses may also be used to collect feedback by members of our editorial or research team, to promote College News products and services, and they may be rented to other firms and/or licensed for promotional purposes. When you provide your email address to us, you agree to receive email from College News. We allow users to “opt-out” of receiving e-mail from outside firms, however, when e-mail information is collected and with each e-mail use of the user’s address you can individually “opt-out” of receiving further e-mail from outside firms and College News. If a user does not choose to “opt-out” at the time the e-mail address is collected, or does not respond to the questions concerning how we may use their email address, the address may be rented and/or licensed for use to outside firms. Offers for which the e-mail address is rented and/or licensed for use require the users to target their offers carefully.

Personal identifying information submitted on portions of our site developed with outside third parties may be shared with those third parties, and the information will be governed by those parties’ privacy policies as well as College News’. College News, nor any of its parent companies or any of its subsidiaries or affiliates, does not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of such third parties.

Collegenews.com users should be aware that when they disclose personal identifying information (e.g., user name, address, company name, telephone number, demographic information, buying information, other data and E-mail address) in discussion forums, chat rooms or other areas that are publicly accessible by others, that information can be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited messages from other posters or parties. College News, nor its parent company or any of its subsidiaries or affiliates, is not responsible for any information that you provide in the above areas.

In the event that the ownership of College News or any of its products are sold or transferred, all lists and data which contains personally identifying information and data including, for example, user name, address, company name, telephone number, demographic information, buying information, other data and e-mail address, will be transferred to the new owner.

Links  
Our Site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information from them. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected on this site.

Changes to this Privacy Policy  
We reserve the right to change our privacy policy from time to time. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect from them, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose this information to third parties.

If at any point we decide that we wish to use personally identifiable information collected from our users in a manner that differs from that stated at the time this information was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice whether or not to consent to our using their personal information in accordance with our updated privacy policy.

Print Subscribers or applicants who do not want their names used in any of the above ways may write and ask to be removed from the promotion list. Requests should be sent to:

One2One Digital manages CollegeNews.com and handles the sites social media.

123 W Madison Street,

Chicago, IL 60602, USA

312-572-7722
